(Ramona:)Again, ew.
(Ramona:)You know, I'd love to hear more
about how you intend to add neutrinos.
(Ramona:)- Could we get a cup of coffee sometime?
- I don't drink coffee.
(Howard:)I do. I love me a cup of Joe.
(Ramona:)It doesn't have to be coffee.
How about dinner?
- I do eat dinner.
- Great. I know a terrific little Italian place.
(Sheldon:)I never eat in strange restaurants.
One runs the risk of non-standard cutlery.
- Excuse me?
- Sheldon lives in fear of the three-tined fork.
(Sheldon:)Three tines is not a fork.
Three tines is a trident.
(Sheldon:)Forks are for eating,
tridents are for ruling the seven seas.
- What if I brought food to your place?
- That would be acceptable.
(Sheldon:)On Mondays, I eat Thai food.
Mee Krob and chicken satay
with extra peanut sauce from Siam Palace.
(Ramona:)You got it. I already have your address.
(Sheldon:)What a nice girl.